A Guide to the John A. Hartford Foundation records, Grants, Series 4 FA1296
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Grants, 1974-1996; 4
  - Mid-Career Fellow - University of Michigan - J. Santinga (84-375), 1984-1986 (Box 421, Folder 3153)
  - Mid-Career Fellow - University of Medicine and Dentistry of New Jersey - R. McDonald (84-376), 1984-1986 (Box 421, Folder 3154)
  - Mid-Career Fellow - Hahnemann University - R. Nathan (84-373), 1984-1986 (Box 421, Folder 3155)
  - Mid-Career Fellow - University of Kentucky - J. Cooper (84-374), 1984-1986 (Box 421, Folder 3156)
  - Mid-Career Fellow - Michigan State University - K. Champney (84-371), 1984-1986 (Box 422, Folder 3157)
  - Mid-Career Fellow - University of Maryland School of Medicine - E. Rogers (84-372), 1984-1986 (Box 422, Folder 3158)
  - Mid-Career Fellow - Johns Hopkins School of Medicine - W. Hazzard (84-379), 1984-1986 (Box 422, Folder 3159)
  - Mid-Career Fellow - Harvard Medical School - R. Besdine (84-378), 1984-1986 (Box 422, Folder 3160)
  - Mid-Career Fellow - University of California Los Angeles - D. Solomon (84-391), 1984-1986 (Box 422, Folder 3161)
  - Mid-Career Fellow - Johns Hopkins School of Medicine - W. Hazzard (83-321), 1983-1985 (Box 422, Folder 3162)
  - Mid-Career Fellow - University of California Los Angeles - D. Solomon (83-322), 1983-1985 (Box 422, Folder 3163)
  - Mid-Career Fellow - University of California Los Angeles - D. Solomon (83-156), 1983-1984 (Box 422, Folder 3164)
  - Mid-Career Fellow - Mt. Sinai School of Medicine - R. Butler (83-157), 1983-1985 (Box 422, Folder 3165)
  - Mid-Career Fellow - Harvard Medical School - R. Besdine (83-155), 1983-1985 (Box 423, Folder 3166)
  - Mid-Career Fellow - Harvard Medical School - R. Besdine (83-320), 1983-1985 (Box 423, Folder 3167)
  - Mid-Career Fellow - Johns Hopkins School of Medicine - W. Hazzard (83-158), 1983-1985 (Box 423, Folder 3168)
  - Mid-Career Fellow - Mt. Sinai School of Medicine - R. Butler (83-319), 1983-1985 (Box 423, Folder 3169)
  - Mid-Career Fellow - Urban Institute - W. Weissert (no grant number), 1983-1984 (Box 423, Folder 3170)
  - Mid-Career Fellow - Mt. Sinai School of Medicine - R. Butler (no grant number), 1983-1984 (Box 423, Folder 3171)
  - Mid-Career Fellow - Emory University - M. Lubin (no grant number), 1983-1984 (Box 423, Folder 3172)
  - Mid-Career Fellow - Veterans Administration - E. Olsen (no grant number), 1983-1984 (Box 423, Folder 3173)
  - Mid-Career Fellow - SUNY Upstate Medican Center - M. Miller (no grant number), 1983-1984 (Box 423, Folder 3174)
  - Mid-Career Fellow - University of California, Los Angeles - J. Beck (84-079), 1985-1987 (Box 423, Folder 3175)
  - Mid-Career Fellow - Virignia Commonwealth University - R. Scott (86-005), 1986-1987 (Box 423, Folder 3176)
  - Mid-Career Fellow - Univesity at Buffalo - J. Edwards (86-006, 1985-1987 (Box 424, Folder 3177)
  - Mid-Career Fellow - University of Connecticut/Harvard Medical School - J. Walker (86-009), 1985-1987 (Box 424, Folder 3178)
  - Mid-Career Fellow - Eastern Virginia Medical School - W. Steiger (86-010), 1986-1987 (Box 424, Folder 3179)
  - Mid-Career Fellow - Olive View Medical Center - F. Kaiser (86-011), 1985-1987 (Box 424, Folder 3180)
  - Mid-Career Fellow - University of Texas, Houston - C. Smythe (86-012), 1985-1987 (Box 424, Folder 3181)
  - Mid-Career Fellow - Harvard University - J. Rowe (86-024), 1985-1987 (Box 424, Folder 3182)
  - Mid-Career Fellow - Johns Hopkins University - J. Burton (86-025), 1985-1987 (Box 424, Folder 3183)
  - Mid-Career Fellow - Mt. Sinai School of Medicine - R. Butler (86-026), 1985-1987 (Box 424, Folder 3184)
  - Mid-Career Fellow - University of California, Los Angeles - D. Solomon (86-027), 1985-1987 (Box 424, Folder 3185)
  - Mid-Career Fellow - University of Mississippi - D. Thomas (86-401), 1986-1988 (Box 424, Folder 3186)
  - Mid-Career Fellow - University of South Florida B. Robinson (86-402), 1986-1988 (Box 424, Folder 3187)
  - Mid-Career Fellow - St. Louis University - D. Miller (86-398), 1986-1988 (Box 425, Folder 3188)
  - Mid-Career Fellow - University - D. Reuben (86-399), 1986-1988 (Box 425, Folder 3189)
  - Mid-Career Fellow - University of Vermont - D. Little (86-403), 1986-1988 (Box 425, Folder 3190)
  - Mid-Career Fellow - Harvard Medical School - J. Rowe (86-404), 1986-1988 (Box 425, Folder 3191)
  - Mid-Career Fellow - Johns Hopkins University - J. Burton (86-405), 1986-1988 (Box 425, Folder 3192)
  - Mid-Career Fellow - University of California, Los Angeles - D. Solomon (86-406), 1986-1988 (Box 425, Folder 3193)
  - Fellow - Prystowsky, Michael, 1985 (Box 425, Folder 3194)
  - Fellow - Addonizio, Victor, 1986 (Box 425, Folder 3195)
  - Fellow - Lachman, Herbert, 1986 (Box 425, Folder 3196)
  - Fellow - Rubens, Craig, 1986 (Box 426, Folder 3197)
  - Biotechnology Transfer Program - Stanford University Medical Center - L. Crowley (84-403), 1984-1985 (Box 426, Folder 3198)
  - Biotechnology Transfer Program - University of California, San Francisco - J. Krevans (84-408), 1984-1985 (Box 426, Folder 3199)
  - Biotechnology Transfer Program Correspondence, 1985 (Box 426, Folder 3200)
  - Biotechnology Transfer Program - Medical School Letters, 1984 (Box 426, Folder 3201)
  - Biotechnology Transfer Program - Rockefeller University Correspondence, 1984 (Box 426, Folder 3202)
  - Biotechnology Transfer Program - "Current File", 1984-1985 (Box 426, Folder 3203)
  - Biotechnology Transfer Program Articles, 1980s (Box 426, Folder 3204)
  - Biotechnology Transfer Program - Working Draft, 1985-1986 (Box 426, Folder 3205)
  - Biotechnology Transfer Program - Correspondence and Call for Applications, 1983-1985 (Box 427, Folder 3206)
  - Biotechnology Transfer Program - Proposals, 1984-1985 (Box 427, Folder 3207-3210)
  - Biotechnology Transfer Program - University of Utah Update, 1985 (Box 427, Folder 3211)
  - Committee on Grants - Consideration of Other Grant Categories, 1983-1984 (Box 427, Folder 3212)
  - Biomedical Research Policy - Background Material, 1980s (Box 428, Folder 3213)
  - Peer Review Process Background Material, 1980s (Box 428, Folder 3214)
  - New England Environmental Mediation Center - W. Humm (80-639), 1980-1985 (Box 428, Folder 3215-3216)
  - Urban Homesteading Assistance Board [UHAB] - R. Pierpont (81-364), 1981-1983 (Box 428, Folder 3217)
  - Urban Homesteading Assistance Board [UHAB] - R. Pierpont (81-364), 1981-1986 (Box 429, Folder 3218-3220)
  - Health Services Improvement Fund - K. Weiner (81-300), 1981-1984 (Box 429, Folder 3221-3223)
  - Health Services Improvement Fund - K. Weiner (81-300), 1981-1984 (Box 430, Folder 3224)
  - RAND Corporation - J. Acton (82-637), 1982-1985 (Box 430, Folder 3225-3226)
  - New York Community Trust Energy Conservation Fund, 1980-1981 (Box 430, Folder 3227-3230)
  - Contra Costa County, California - S. Hoffman (82-526), 1982-1985 (Box 431, Folder 3231-3234)
  - Contra Costa County, California - S. Hoffman (82-526) Separated media 2014:023:021 - "The Economics of Energy Management", 1984 June 15; Betamax videotape (Box 2014:023:021, Folder 3234)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Access copy currently unavailable. Please contact a RAC archivist for further instruction.
  - Contra Costa County, California - S. Hoffman (82-526) Separated media 2014:023:022 - "The Shift and Save Case"., c. 1984; U-matic videotape (Box 2014:023:022, Folder 3234)
  - Contra Costa County, California - S. McPeak (83-208), 1983-1985 (Box 431, Folder 3235)
  - Energy Task Force - C. Chittenden (82-629), 1982-1984 (Box 431, Folder 3236)
  - Recommendations to JAHF on Energy Program, by Curt Biren, 1982 April (Box 431, Folder 3237)
  - Energy Program Loan Documents, 1981-1982 (Box 431, Folder 3238)
    Restricted material.
  - Mount Sinai School of Medicine - A. Kay (83-201), 1983-1987 (Box 432, Folder 3239-3242)
  - Gerontological Society of America - J. Corman (84-030), 1984-1989 (Box 432, Folder 3243)
  - Gerontological Society of America - J. Corman (84-030), 1984-1989 (Box 433, Folder 3244)
  - United Seniors Consumer Cooperative - J. Firman (84-168), 1984-1986 (Box 433, Folder 3245-3246)
  - United Seniors Health Cooperative - J. Firman (85-236), 1985-1989 (Box 433, Folder 3247-3249)
  - United Seniors Health Cooperative - J. Firman (85-236), 1985-1989 (Box 434, Folder 3250-3251)
  - United Seniors Health Cooperative - J. Firman (89-228), 1989-1991 (Box 434, Folder 3252-3254)
  - Brookdale Center on Aging/Research Foundation of City University of New York (CUNY) - R. Dobrof (84-469), 1984-1988 (Box 434, Folder 3255-3256)
  - Brookdale Center on Aging - R. Dobrof (84-469), 1984-1988 (Box 435, Folder 3257-3258)
  - Brookdale Center on Aging - R. Dobrof (84-469) Separated media 2014:023:023 - "In Care of - Families and Their Elders", c. 1987; VHS videotape (Box 2014:023:023, Folder 3234)
  - Brookdale Center on Aging - R. Dobrof (84-129), 1984-1985 (Box 435, Folder 3259-3260)
  - Community Care Organization of Milwaukee County, Wisconsin - J. Donohue (86-130), 1986-1989 (Box 435, Folder 3262-3263)
  - Louis Harris and Associates - M. Baker (85-237), 1985-1987 (Box 436, Folder 3264-3268)
  - Community Care Organization of Milwaukee County, Wisconsin - K. Shoaf (86-130), 1986-1989 (Box 437, Folder 3269-3272)
  - National Governors' Association - R. Curtis (consultant), 1987-1988 (Box 437, Folder 3273-3274)
  - Beth Israel Hospital - J. Avorn (85-056), 1985-1988 (Box 438, Folder 3275-3278)
  - Beth Israel Hospital - J. Avorn (88-220), 1988-1989 (Box 438, Folder 3279)
  - National Governors' Association - R. Curtis (consultant), 1987-1988 (Box 438, Folder 3280-3281)
  - Brigham and Women's Hospital - A. Epstein (83-134), 1983-1989 (Box 439, Folder 3282-3287)
  - University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill - W. Weissert (84-205), 1984-1989 (Box 440, Folder 3288-3294)
  - University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill - A. Hartzema (88-028), 1988-1993 (Box 441, Folder 3295-3299)
  - University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill - A. Hartzema (88-028), 1988-1993 (Box 442, Folder 3300-3305)
  - University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill - A. Hartzema (88-028), 1988-1993 (Box 443, Folder 3306-3307)
  - University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill - M. Williams (89-162), 1989-1990 (Box 443, Folder 3308-3309)
  - University of California, San Francisco - H. Lipton (86-123), 1986-1990 (Box 443, Folder 3310-3311)
  - University of California, San Francisco - H. Lipton (86-123), 1986-1990 (Box 444, Folder 3312-3314)
  - University of Florida - W. Elmore (86-120), 1986-1991 (Box 444, Folder 3315-3317)
  - University of Florida - W. Elmore (86-120), 1986-1991 (Box 445, Folder 3318-3323)
  - University of Florida - W. Elmore (86-120), 1986-1991 (Box 446, Folder 3324-3325)
  - Central Iowa Health Association - R. Burnett (80-469), 1980-1984 (Box 446, Folder 3326-3327)
  - Institute for the Future - R. Johansen (83-200), 1983-1985 (Box 446, Folder 3328-3330)
  - National Governors' Association - R. Curtis (82-666), 1982-1987 (Box 447, Folder 3331-3337)
  - National Governors' Association - R. Curtis (82-666), 1982-1987 (Box 448, Folder 3338-3341)
  - Washington Business Group on Health - W. Goldbeck (83-610), 1983-1985 (Box 448, Folder 3342-3343)
  - Health Choice, Inc. - S. Kaufman (82-581), 1982-1984 (Box 449, Folder 3344-3348)
  - Health Choice, Inc. - S. Kaufman (83-181), 1983-1985 (Box 450, Folder 3349-3351)
  - Health Choice, Inc. - R. O'Brien/S. Kaufman (84-448), 1984-1987 (Box 450, Folder 3352-3353)
  - Health Services Foundation - W. Elliott (79-013), 1979-1983 (Box 450, Folder 3354)
  - Health Services Foundation - W. Elliott (79-013), 1979-1983 (Box 451, Folder 3355-3356)
  - Health Services Foundation - W. Elliott (81-368), 1981-1983 (Box 451, Folder 3357-3360)
  - Health Services Foundation - W. Elliott (82-685), 1982-1983 (Box 451, Folder 3361)
  - Council of Medical Specialty Societies - R. Wilbur (81-245), 1981-1985 (Box 452, Folder 3362-3364)
  - Council of Medical Specialty Societies - R. Wilbur (89-219), 1989-1991 (Box 452, Folder 3365-3367)
  - Council of Medical Specialty Societies - R. Wilbur (89-219) Separated media 2014:023:024 - "Patient Injury Prevention Program - Courtrooms are for Doctors, Not Lawyers"., 1984; 2 audiotapes (Box 2014:023:024, Folder 3367)
  - Council of Medical Specialty Societies - R. Wilbur (89-219) Separated media 2014:023:025 - "Patient Injury Prevention Program - Informed Consent - Its Meaning and Application"., 1985; 2 audiotapes (Box 2014:023:025, Folder 3367)
  - Duke University Center for Health Policy and Education - D. Eddy (82-620), 1982-1986 (Box 453, Folder 3368-3372)
  - Duke University - D. Eddy (86-374), 1986-1990 (Box 453, Folder 3373-3374)
  - Duke University - D. Eddy (86-374), 1986-1990 (Box 454, Folder 3375-3376)
  - Center for Policy Studies - W. McClure (82-516), 1982-1986 (Box 454, Folder 3377-3380)
  - Center for Policy Studies - W. McClure (82-516), 1982-1986 (Box 455, Folder 3381)
  - Center for Policy Studies - D. Shaller/W. McClure (84-358), 1984-1987 (Box 455, Folder 3382-3387)
  - Center for Policy Studies - D. Shaller/W. McClure (84-358), 1984-1987 (Box 456, Folder 3388-3389)
  - Center for Policy Studies - D. Shaller (87-015), 1987-1989 (Box 456, Folder 3390-3393)
  - Center for Policy Studies - D. Shaller (87-015), 1987-1989 (Box 457, Folder 3394-3400)
  - Center for Policy Studies - W. McClure (89-016), 1989-1991 (Box 458, Folder 3401-3404)
  - Center for Health Policy Development - E. Neuschler (88-237), 1988-1989 (Box 458, Folder 3405-3406)
  - Center for Health Policy Development - T. Riley (89-081), 1989-1991 (Box 459, Folder 3407-3411)
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) - Housing (89-008), 1989-1991 (Box 459, Folder 3412-3413)
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) - Housing (89-008), 1989-1991 (Box 460, Folder 3414-3418)
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) - Housing (90-080), 1990-1991 (Box 460, Folder 3419-3420)
  - Biotechnology Transfer Program - Chronology and Application, 1983-1985 (Box 461, Folder 3421)
  - Biotechnology Transfer Program - Correspondence with Applicants, 1984-1985 (Box 461, Folder 3422)
  - Biotechnology Transfer Program - Background Information, 1984-1985 (Box 461, Folder 3423-3424)
  - Biotechnology Transfer Program - Potential Applicants, 1985-1986 (Box 461, Folder 3425)
  - Biotechnology Transfer Program - University of Washington Research Conference, 1986 June (Box 461, Folder 3426)
  - Biotechnology Transfer Program - Technology Transfer Society Symposium, 1986 June (Box 461, Folder 3427)
  - Biotechnology Transfer Program - Program Planning Materials, 1985-1986 (Box 462, Folder 3428)
  - Biotechnology Transfer Program - Other Models for Technology Transfer, 1985-1987 (Box 462, Folder 3429)
  - Biotechnology Transfer Program - Advisory Board Resumes and Correspondence, 1984 (Box 462, Folder 3430-3431)
  - Biotechnology Transfer Program - Advisory Board Background Materials, 1984-1985 (Box 462, Folder 3432)
  - Biotechnology Transfer Program - Response to Letter, 1984-1985 (Box 462, Folder 3433)
  - Biotechnology Transfer Program - Legal Matters, 1984-1985 (Box 462, Folder 3434)
  - Biotechnology Transfer Program - Replies to Letter, 1984-1985 (Box 462, Folder 3435)
  - Biotechnology Transfer Program - Partnership Recommendations, 1984 (Box 463, Folder 3436)
  - Biotechnology Transfer Program - University of California San Diego, 1985 (Box 463, Folder 3437)
  - Biotechnology Transfer Program - OMEC International, 1984 (Box 463, Folder 3438)
  - Biotechnology Transfer Program - The Rockefeller University, 1985 (Box 463, Folder 3439)
  - Biotechnology Transfer Program - University of Texas, Dallas, 1984-1985 (Box 463, Folder 3440-3441)
  - Biotechnology Transfer Program - Stanford University School of Medicine, 1984 (Box 463, Folder 3442)
  - Biotechnology Transfer Program - Background Information, 1980s (Box 463, Folder 3443-3444)
  - Unemployment Maintenance Organization (no grant number), 1984 (Box 464, Folder 3445)
  - St. Vincent's Hospital Chronic Pain Institute (no grant number), 1984 (Box 464, Folder 3446)
  - Cocaine Treatment Center (no grant number), 1984 (Box 464, Folder 3447)
  - Nuclear Disaster Response (no grant number), 1982-1984 (Box 464, Folder 3448)
  - Chelation Therapy (no grant number), 1984 (Box 464, Folder 3449)